<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andrew Zhang</title>
    <link>https://aspartate.github.io/personal_website/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Andrew Zhang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:27:44 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aspartate.github.io/personal_website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 3</title>
      <link>https://aspartate.github.io/personal_website/blog/week-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:27:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aspartate.github.io/personal_website/blog/week-3/</guid>
      <description>hello world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 2: 2D Design</title>
      <link>https://aspartate.github.io/personal_website/blog/week-2-2d-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 01:47:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aspartate.github.io/personal_website/blog/week-2-2d-design/</guid>
      <description>For this project we were asked to model two real-world components in Fusion 360 and create an assembly. I decided to model a PVC bulkhead which I had recently purchased for a hydroponics project. The bulkhead came without a nut, however, so I decided to model &amp;amp; 3D print one myself. Because this was my first time working with Fusion (I previously did all modeling in TinkerCAD), I figured this bulkhead offered a good mix of features to model without being too complicated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1: Final Project Proposal</title>
      <link>https://aspartate.github.io/personal_website/blog/week-1-final-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 17:11:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aspartate.github.io/personal_website/blog/week-1-final-project/</guid>
      <description>For my final project, I have a couple of ideas revolving around robotics and control systems. I&amp;rsquo;ve always been fascinated with the ability of humans, through technology, to control things outside of our own body. Below are several ideas which I would like to explore.
EEG-controlled robot. I have this toy bluetooth-enabled EEG from a Star Wars Force Trainer kit which I had purchased a while back specifically for the purpose of doing some cool things with in terms of brain-machine interfaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bugs to be Squashed</title>
      <link>https://aspartate.github.io/personal_website/blog/bugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 01:49:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aspartate.github.io/personal_website/blog/bugs/</guid>
      <description>Here are the bugs I need to fix:
 The modals don&amp;rsquo;t work in gallery mode. Also when making a new gallery post I get a weird json error, which goes away when I comment out a block of github stuff. When a blog post is opened, the header menu is in a weird place and covers up some of the text. When a blog post is opened, the next/previous navigation buttons are too close together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>https://aspartate.github.io/personal_website/blog/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aspartate.github.io/personal_website/blog/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Please ignore, this is for my own edification.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me.</title>
      <link>https://aspartate.github.io/personal_website/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:39:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aspartate.github.io/personal_website/about/</guid>
      <description>I’m a junior at Harvard College studying Human Developmental and Regenerative Biology. I believe that technological solutions are urgently needed to augment and expand the reach of limited healthcare resources in underserved areas around the world. I’m heavily involved in the nonprofit Global Alliance for Medical Innovation, an incubator for budding healthtech startups. Talk to me anytime about global health, technology, neuroscience, or magic tricks!
 Note: I&amp;rsquo;m trying to get gallery mode to work but am running into some issues with modals at the moment&amp;hellip;so please excuse the boring blog post format for now.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
